<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClothesDrop</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">Terms and Conditions
\n
\nLast updated: May 11, 2017
\n
\nThese Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") govern your relationship with Clothes Drop mobile application (the "Service") operated by posAbilities Association of British Columbia ("us", "we", or "our").
\n
\nPlease read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using our Clothes Drop mobile application (the "Service").
\n
\nYour access to and use of the Service is based on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.
\n
\nBy accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms and accept all legal consequences. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, in whole or in part, please do not use the Service.
\n
\nAccounts
\n
\nWhen you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account on our Service.
\n
\nYou are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service.
\n
\nYou agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.
\n
\nYou may not use as a username the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorization, or a name that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene.
\n
\nIntellectual Property
\n
\nThe Service and all contents, including but not limited to text, images, graphics or code are the property of posAbilities Association of British Columbia and are protected by copyright, trademarks, database and other intellectual property rights. You may display and copy, download or print portions of the material from the different areas of the Service only for your own non-commercial use. Any other use is strictly prohibited and may violate copyright, trademark and other laws. These Terms do not grant you a license to use any trademark of posAbilities Association of British Columbia or its affiliates. You further agree not to use, change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from the Service.
\n
\nLinks To Other Web Sites
\n
\nThe Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by posAbilities Association of British Columbia.
\n
\nposAbilities Association of British Columbia has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that posAbilities Association of British Columbia shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such websites or services.
\n
\nWe strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.
\n
\nTermination
\n
\nWe may terminate or suspend access to our Service immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including, without limitation, if you breach the Terms.
\n
\nAll provisions of the Terms shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.
\n
\nUpon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service.
\n
\nIndemnification
\n
\nYou agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless posAbilities Association of British Columbia, its principals, officers, directors, representatives, employees, contractors, licensors, licensees, suppliers and agents, from and against any claims, losses, damages, losses, obligations, costs, actions or demands.
\n
\nThese include but are not limited to: (a) legal and accounting fees resulting from your use of the Service; (b) your breach of any of these Terms; (c) anything you post on or upload to the Service; and (d) any activity related to your account. This includes any negligent or illegal conduct by you, any person or entity accessing the Service using your account whether such access is obtained via fraudulent or illegal means.
\n
\nLimitation Of Liability
\n
\nposAbilities Association of British Columbia, its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, shall not be liable for any loss or damage, direct or indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, economic loss, loss or damage to electronic media or data, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of the Service; (ii) your inability to access or use the Service; (iii) any conduct or content of any third-party on or related to the Service; (iiv) any content obtained from or through the Service; and (v) the unauthorized access to, use of or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other claim in law, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.
\n
\nDisclaimer And Non-Waiver of Rights
\n
\nposAbilities Association of British Columbia makes no guarantees, representations or warranties of any kind as regards the website and associated technology. Any purportedly applicable warranties, terms and conditions are excluded, to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance, except as provided for under the laws of any province in Canada. In such cases, the provincial law shall apply to the extent necessary.
\n
\nposAbilities Association of British Columbia its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.
\n
\nIf you breach any of these Terms and posAbilities Association of British Columbia chooses not to immediately act, or chooses not to act at all, posAbilities Association of British Columbia will still be entitled to all rights and remedies at any later date, or in any other situation, where you breach these Terms. posAbilities Association of British Columbia does not waive any of its rights. posAbilities Association of British Columbia shall not be responsible for any purported breach of these Terms caused by circumstances beyond its control. A person who is not a party to these Terms shall have no rights of enforcement.
\n
\nYou may not assign, sub-license or otherwise transfer any of your rights under these Terms.
\n
\nExclusions
\n
\nAs set out, above, some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the limitations above may not apply to you. Provincial laws of Canada may apply to certain products and service provided.
\n
\nGoverning Law
\n
\nThese Terms shall be governed by, and interpreted and enforced in accordance with, the laws in the Province of British Columbia and the laws of Canada, as applicable.
\n
\nIf any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, then any remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements, oral or otherwise, regarding the Service.
\n
\nChanges
\n
\nWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will make reasonable efforts to provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.
\n
\nBy continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, in whole or in part, please stop using the website and the Service.
\n
\nContact Us
\n
\nIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.
\n\nPrivacy Policy
\n
\nLast updated: May 11, 2017
\n
\nposAbilities Association of British Columbia ("us", "we", or "our") operates the Clothes Drop mobile application (the "Service").
\n
\nPersonal Information Collect, Use, Disclosure and Consent
\n
\nPersonal Information may include your name, email address, age, home address, phone number, marital status, income, credit history, medical information, education, employment information and social registration numbers.
\n
\nWe are committed to providing our clients, customers, members ("you", "your" or "them") with exceptional service. Providing exceptional service may involve the collection, use and, at times, the disclosure of your Personal Information. Protecting your Personal Information is one of our highest priorities. While we have always respected your privacy and safeguarded all Personal Information, we have strengthened our commitment to this goal. This is to continue to provide exceptional service to you and to comply with all laws regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information. We will inform you of why and how we collect, use and disclose Personal Information; obtain your consent, as required; and handle Personal Information according to applicable law. Our privacy commitment includes ensuring the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your Personal Information and allowing you to request access to, and correction of, your personal information.
\n
\nThis page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.
\n
\nWe will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
\n
\nWe will only collect Personal Information that is necessary to fulfill the following purposes:
\n
\nTo verify identity;
\n
\nTo identify your preferences;
\n
\nTo open and manage an account;
\n
\nTo ensure you receive a high standard of service;
\n
\nTo meet regulatory requirements;
\n
\nOther legal reasons as apply to the goods and services requested.
\n
\nWe will obtain your consent to collect, use or disclose Personal Information. In some cases, we can do so without your consent (see below). You can provide consent orally, in writing, electronically or through an authorized representative.
\n
\nYou provide implied consent where our purpose for collecting using or disclosing your Personal Information would be considered obvious or reasonable in the circumstances. Consent may also be implied where you have notice and a reasonable opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for mail-outs, marketing or fundraising and you do not opt-out.
\n
\nWe may collect, use or disclose Personal Information without the consent:
\n
\nWhen permitted or required by law;
\n
\nIn an emergency that threatens an individual\'s life, health, or personal security;
\n
\nWhen the Personal Information is available from a public source;
\n
\nWhen we require legal advice from a lawyer;
\n
\nFor the purposes of collecting a debt or protection from fraud;
\n
\nOther legally established reasons.
\n
\nWe will not sell your Personal Information to other parties unless consent has been provided or implied. We retain your Personal Information for the time necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or a legal or business purpose. We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that your Personal Information is accurate and complete. You may request correction to your Personal Information to ensure its accuracy and completeness. A request must be in writing and provide sufficient detail to identify your Personal Information and the correction being sought.
\n
\nWe are committed to ensuring the security of your Personal Information and may use passwords, encryption, firewalls, restricted employee access or other methods, in our discretion. We will use appropriate security measures when destroying your Personal Information such as shredding documents or deleting electronically stored information, in our discretion.
\n
\nLog Data
\n
\nWhen you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use and other statistics ("Log Data").
\n
\nIn addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service\'s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.
\n
\nLocation Information
\n
\nSubject to the provisions regarding the use of your Personal Information, above, we may use and store information about your location. We use this information for the purposes set out above, and specifically, to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service. You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at anytime, through your mobile device settings.
\n
\nCookies
\n
\nCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer\'s hard drive.
\n
\nWe use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. If you do not instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, your consent to our use of your Personal Information may be implied.
\n
\nService Providers
\n
\nWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
\n
\nThese third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
\n
\nCompliance With Laws
\n
\nAs set out above, and for clarity, we will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.
\n
\nSecurity
\n
\nThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
\n
\nLinks To Other Sites
\n
\nOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party\'s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
\n
\nWe have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
\n
\nChildren\'s Privacy
\n
\nOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Minor").
\n
\nWe do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from Minors. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Minor has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from Minors without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
\n
\nChanges To This Privacy Policy
\n
\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
\n
\nYou are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
\n
\nIf we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
\n
\nContact Us
\n
\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.</string>
</resources>
